[
    {
        "question": "What is the Iron Bank’s representative, called?",
        "a": "Quorin Halfhand",
        "b": "Xaro Xhoan Daxon",
        "c": "Howard from the Halifax",
        "d": "Tycho Nestoris",
        "ans": "Tycho Nestoris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was responsible for the creation of the Night King?",
        "a": "The Lord of Light",
        "b": "The Children of the Forest",
        "c": "The Drowned God",
        "d": "The First Men",
        "ans": "The Children of the Forest"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Hodor called before he got his tragic door-holding nickname?",
        "a": "Wylis",
        "b": "Horys",
        "c": "Myrys",
        "d": "Gladys",
        "ans": "Wylis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dany’s dragons are called Drogon, Viserion and __?",
        "a": "Dougal",
        "b": "Vhagar",
        "c": "Rhaegar",
        "d": "Balerion",
        "ans": "Rhaegar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Ned Stark’s predecessor as Robert Baratheon’s Hand?",
        "a": "Jaime Lannister",
        "b": "Jon Arryn",
        "c": "Tywin Lannister",
        "d": "Ser Jorah Mormont",
        "ans": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "Iwan Rheon(Ramsay Bolton) was almost cast as which character?",
        "a": "Jon Snow",
        "b": "Gendry",
        "c": "Podrick Payne",
        "d": "Rob Stark",
        "ans": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said:'I don’t plan on knitting by the fire while men fight for me'?",
        "a": "Lyanna Mormont",
        "b": "Sansa Stark",
        "c": "Brienne of Tarth",
        "d": "Olenna Tyrell",
        "ans": "Lyanna Mormont"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who’s this grizzled chap with Ser Jorah and Daenerys?",
        "a": "Ser Elrick Sarsfield",
        "b": "Ser Balon Swann",
        "c": "Ser Royland Degore",
        "d": "Ser Barristan Selmy",
        "ans": "Ser Barristan Selmy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters is dead?",
        "a": "Jaqen H’Gar",
        "b": "Nymeria the direwolf",
        "c": "Hot Pie",
        "d": "Eddison Tollett",
        "ans": "Eddison Tollett"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the House of Black and White?",
        "a": "Qarth",
        "b": "Braavos",
        "c": "Meereen",
        "d": "No one knows",
        "ans": "Braavos"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which King’s Landing slum did Gendry grow up?",
        "a": "Flea Bottom",
        "b": "Rat Bottom",
        "c": "Rhaenys’s Hill",
        "d": "Dragonpit",
        "ans": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Arya’s sword?",
        "a": "Ice",
        "b": "Pointy",
        "c": "Fang",
        "d": "Needle",
        "ans": "Needle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the Red Keep’s chief mouser (RIP) called?",
        "a": "Ser Pounce",
        "b": "Maester Paw",
        "c": "Lady Claws",
        "d": "The Bastard",
        "ans": "Ser Pounce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which relative did Euron Greyjoy murder to take the Iron Islands?",
        "a": "His brother",
        "b": "His uncle",
        "c": "His nephew",
        "d": "His cousin",
        "ans": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the first words King Robert said to Ned Stark in episode 1 of season 1?",
        "a": "You’ve got fat.",
        "b": "You’ve not changed.",
        "c": "You look old.",
        "d": "Your hair looks terrible.",
        "ans": "You’ve got fat."
    },
    {
        "question": "The actor who played Brother Ray also played which antique-loving TV scoundrel?",
        "a": "David Dickinson",
        "b": "Del Boy Trotter",
        "c": "Rodney Trotter",
        "d": "Lovejoy",
        "ans": "Lovejoy"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many kings and queens of Westeros did Lord Varys serve?",
        "a": "2",
        "b": "3",
        "c": "4",
        "d": "5",
        "ans": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who had the honour of killing Petyr Baelish?",
        "a": "Jon Snow",
        "b": "Sansa Stark",
        "c": "Brienne",
        "d": "Arya Stark",
        "ans": "Arya Stark"
    },
    {
        "question": "The smaller denominations of the Gold Dragon coin are the copper penny and the ___?",
        "a": "Silver stallion",
        "b": "Golden goose",
        "c": "Silver stag",
        "d": "Bronze bull",
        "ans": "Silver stag"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose last words were: 'Give me something for the pain, and let me die'?",
        "a": "Stannis Baratheon",
        "b": "Hodor",
        "c": "Robert Baratheon",
        "d": "Walder Frey",
        "ans": "c"
    }
]